Moronke Oladesu

Ikeja roladesu@gmail.com 09059838075

Ronke is a young, driven and enthusiastic graduate of geophysics from the Obafemi Awolowo University with experience in the use of Adobe illustrator, Photoshop as well as Microsoft office. She is capable of working with least supervision due to her leadership capabilities and is willing to learn and grow in order to develop herself in accordance with the evolving world.

Willing to relocate to: USA - Canada, KY - Australia

Work Experience

Freelance Graphic Designer

self-employed - Lagos July 2021 to Present

Been creating logos, designs for Instagram posts, branding for different startups. Been privileged to work with at least 2 startups.

A pharmaceutical Business and A transportation company.

Graphics Designer/Social media Manager

TheElects - Lagos October 2019 to July 2021

In charge of the company's instagram page which was a major point of sales. Account followers grew \sim 35% while I was there and there was increase in engagement.

In charge of the daily uploads on the page. made at least 5 posts per day.

Client Service/Quality control

DM Holdings Ltd January 2019 to September 2019

Client Service o Manages the transmission of the a Tv show Leadership role

Treasurer

Obafemi Awolowo University 2015 to 2016

o Helped in monitoring and analyzing the departmental financial history for the purpose of forecasting and developing future cash management strategies.

Education

B.Sc. in Applied Geophysics

Obafemi Awolowo University 2012 to 2017

Pre-degree

Obafemi Awolowo University November 2011 to July 2012

High school or equivalent

Christ the Redeemer's International Secondary School September 2005 to July 2011

Skills

- Photoshop (2 years)
- Illustrator (3 years)
- Microsoft word (3 years)
- Microsoft excel (3 years)
- Corel painter (1 year)
- Digital marketing (2 years)
- Winresist (4 years)
- Graphic design (3 years)

Certifications and Licenses

Customer relationship management

December 2018 to Present

Effective presentations

December 2018 to Present

HSE 1&2

September 2016 to Present

Assessments

Memorization & Recall — Proficient

August 2019

Committing product or merchandise information to memory and recalling it at a later time.

Full results: Proficient

Basic attention to detail — Expert

August 2021

Identifying differences in materials, following instructions, and detecting details among distracting information

Full results: Expert

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.